Welcome to Stock Market,
I welcome you all to the channel of Coming Stock Market.
If you have not yet liked, shared and subscribed to our other channel
English Love, then
please
like, share and subscribe tomorrow.
If you have
not yet seen this video, then I will give the link of the video
in the description box, you can
go and watch it. Today we are going to talk about
a stock of the auto sector which can prove to be a feature multi-
fool. So let's start the video. So
first of all we will see the
balance sheet of the company. If we talk about balance,
here you can see reserve and sir
plus. Let's talk about it for a while.
You can see the WhatsApp plus first, which the
company has, which is Rs. 8829 in 2019,
which you can see in the middle of thousand,
6948.
If we talk about 2021, then in 2021 there
is a surprise of Rs. 660183 caller, if we talk about
long-term  If we talk about debt, then we
can also see that the debt of the company,
which is currently Rs
2509.28
crore, and in 2020, you can see that
instead of Rs 13,539 crore, it would have been Rs 1353 crore. So, let
us now talk about the strength of the company. Let us
talk about
how many classes the company has. Let us go down and see what is that. So,
you can see that earlier the
company had debt i.e. Rs
1309.21 crore
and now what it has is Rs
800.21 crore. Right now the company has debt.
If we talk about the shareholder pattern, then
you can see that
currently the promoter of the company has
more than one percent shareholder.
If we talk about it, if we
look at it through the graph, then you can see that the
graph which you see in blue color is the
product, after that
31.04  After that you can see that the
public has
31.2 percent, if we talk about f5, then
you can see that it has
17.04 percent, if we talk about desk then it has only one
point
214 percent,
as long as this is about shareholder pattern
and let's see if we are crazy, so
you can see what the company
works in, this company can see that it
makes light, alternative electricity, service,
speed network, these people who work in the company,
this article, subscription network, they
work in all these things, if we
talk about difference then in difference, let's
see what the company makes,
click on difference and see
that now you can see that the actor has
come in difference, let's see on the company's website,
whatever you can see, what
things the company makes in defense,
you can see these vehicles, the company makes,
what all does it make in difference, so you can see,
all these are of the company,
these are the vehicles which the army uses,
you can see, so this company
You can also check by going to the website of Tata Motors.
If we talk according to market capitalization, then
Tata
Motors is number one in its sector, after that you
can talk about Ashok Leyland. After that, if we
talk about Tata Motors DVR, then if we
talk about the net profit of this company, then
you can see that the net profit of this company is ₹ 100 crore, that is
why the
business of the company was stagnant,
first
353 products, then 2070 products, so
in this company you can see many types of
profit, you can see that if we talk about the news, then
Ashok Leyland has
shown a growth of more than five percent
and along with this, if you see, then if you
talk about any sale of this company, then
you can see this company here,
which you can see here that this
company Ashok Leyland has seen an
increase of 14 percent in its sales in September, that is, the
total unit sale is that
units of vehicles have been sold, if
apart from this, other users  If you do this, you
can see that this model is
subscribed to,
you can see that it is
set at 12% more than the normal rate, just over 1% in the market. So, if we
talk about this company, let's talk about today's performance. We have
already come to the website, you
can see Ashok Leyland.
If we come here, here we have
company information. In the company information,
you can see here the
shareholder pattern. If we talk about it,
you will see
51.54, which I already told you about. And
here you can see France Adult, which
right now this company also gives dividend. And if
we talk about it, if we talk about 52-week high,
you can see that it is
more than 140 rupees, 143 rupees. How much did it
close at, 135, it is six percent higher. If we talk about its returns,
you can see
its returns. If we compare it, you can see
today's returns.  If we talk, you can see that
it is running at 35.75. If we talk about 5 years and 15
days, then you will get a
return of more than 2.1 percent. If we
talk about one month, then you will get a return of about 12
percent. If we talk about six months, then
you can see that it is giving a return of about 11 percent at 11 percent.
If we talk about a year, then 36 percent
is a 3637 percent return. If we
look at the maximum chart pattern, then it will keep
giving you a return of 5596 percent. So
you can consider this company.
Also, it
can prove to be a multiplexer in features. So, I
leave it to you in the description, the
decision is yours. So, if you liked the
video cassette, then please
like, share and subscribe to the channel and do
reply in the comment box about how you liked the video.
Then we will meet in the next video, till then
bye-bye.